Guide to the Paul Jeffrey Papers, 1969-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series IV: Music Manuscripts, 1983-2003 and undated, (103 boxes)
  - Hello, Dolly! (Box 75)
  - Here Comes that Rainy Day (Box 75)
  - Here's That Rainy Day (Box 75)
  - Hi Fly (Box 75)
  - Hicks Time, (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Hip Or Critical? (Box 76)
  - Hipnotism (Box 76)
  - Hobnobbin' (Box 76)
  - Home Stretch (Box 76)
  - Hot House, (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - How Deep Is The Ocean, (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - How Do I Look in Blue? (Box 76)
  - How High the Moon (Box 76)
  - Hump, (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Hurricane Sue (Box 76)
  - I Ain't Gonna Ask No More (Box 77)
  - I Can Dream, Can't I (Box 77)
  - I Can't Get Started, (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - I Don't Know How to Love Him (Box 77)
  - I Got Rhythm (Box 77)
  - I Know That You Know (Box 77)
  - I Let a Song Go Out of My Heart (Box 77)
  - I Married an Angel (Box 77)
  - I Mean You, (3 folders) (Box 77)
  - I Should Care (Box 77)
  - I Thought It Was Understood, (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - I Will Wait for You (Box 77)
  - Ides of March, The (Box 77)
  - If I Were A Bell (Box 77)
  - I'll Be Around (Box 77)
  - I'll Keep Loving You (Box 77)
  - I'll Never Stop Loving You (Box 77)
  - I'll Remember April (Box 77)
  - I'm Beginning to See the Light (Box 78)
  - Impressions (Box 78)
  - In A Mellow Tone, (3 folders) (Box 78)
  - In A Sentimental Mood (Box 78)
  - In Love in L.A., (3 folders) (Box 78)
  - In Memorium Frankie Newton (Box 78)
  - In the Land of Oo-Bla-Dee (Box 78)
  - In The Mood, (4 folders) (Box 78)
  - In Vogue, (4 folders) (Box 79)
  - Incentive (Box 79)
  - Inner Urge, (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Inner Visions (Box 79)
  - Inspiration, (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Interlude (Box 79)
  - Interstate 95 South (Box 79)
  - Introspection (Box 79)
  - Is That So (Box 80)
  - Isn't She Lovely, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Isotope, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Israel (Box 80)
  - It Ain't Necessarily So, (4 folders) (Box 80)
  - It Could Happen to You (Box 80)
  - It Had To Be You (Box 80)
  - It's Alright with Me, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - I've Never Been in Love Before, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Jackie-ing, (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Jamba (Box 81)
  - Japanese Suite, (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Jazz Corner, (3 folders) (Box 81)
  - Jeru (Box 81)
  - Jessica's Day, (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Jinriksha (Box 81)
  - Jitterbug Waltz, (8 folders) (Box 82)
  - Jodo, (4 folders) (Box 83)
  - Juicy Fruit, (3 folders) (Box 83)
  - Juicy Fruit (arr. Murtha) (Box 83)
  - Jump Monk (Box 83)
  - Junior, (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Just the Facts (Box 84)
  - Just The Way You Are (Box 84)
  - Just You Just Me (Box 84)
  - Kid from Red Bank, The (Box 84)
  - Kids Are Pretty People (Box 84)
  - Killer Joe (Box 84)
  - Kiwi Bird (Box 84)
  - Kojo Time, (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Ko-Ko (Box 84)
  - La Bossa, (3 folders) (Box 84)
  - LA Neveda Blues (Box 84)
  - La Shelle (Box 84)
  - Lady Barbara (Box 84)
  - Lament (Box 85)
  - Land of Make Believe (Box 85)
  - Landmarks, (4 folders) (Box 85)
  - LaShelle (Box 85)
  - Last Train From Overbrook (Box 85)
  - Launching Pad (Box 85)
  - Lazy Bird, (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - Leslie, (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - Liber Tad Ahorra (Box 85)
  - Light Blue, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Light Within (Box 86)
  - Like A Son (Box 86)
  - Like What is This, (3 folders) (Box 86)
  - Lil' Willie (Box 86)
  - Little Brown Jug, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Little John Special (Box 86)
  - Little Pixie II, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Little Rootie Tootie, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Little Suzie (Box 87)
  - Little Willie Leaps, (4 folders) (Box 87)
  - Liv House Blues (Box 87)
  - Liza (Box 87)
  - Locomotive (Box 87)
  - Long Long Wait, The, (2 folders) (Box 87)
  - Long Long Wait, The, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Los Hermanos De Bop (Box 88)
  - Love Handles (Box 88)
  - Love Is Here (Box 88)
  - Love the Feelin' (Box 88)
  - Lullaby in Rhythm (Box 88)
  - Magenta Haze (Box 88)
  - Magic Flea, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Main Stem, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Mango Mangue, (3 folders) (Box 88)
  - Manhattan Fever (Box 89)
  - Marmaduke, (4 folders) (Box 89)
  - Masquerade (Box 89)
  - Meeting, The, (5 folders) (Box 89)
  - Melchizedek, (4 folders) (Box 90)
  - Mellow Soul (Box 90)
  - Mexicali Nose (Box 90)
  - Midnight Sun, (3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Milanese Blues, (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Miles Ahead, (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Milestones, (3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Mini Drum Suite (Box 91)
  - Minister's Son, (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - Minor March, (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - Minor Scene (Box 91)
  - Minor's Holiday (Box 91)
  - Miro (Box 91)
  - Misterioso, (3 folders) (Box 91)
  - Mo' Joe (Box 91)
  - Modus Operandi (Box 91)
  - Moment's Notice, (2 folders) (Box 92)
  - Mommy, (4 folders) (Box 92)
  - Monklets (Box 92)
  - Monk's Mood, (4 folders) (Box 92)
  - Monsieur Lesbois in Paris (Box 92)
  - Montmarte (Box 92)
  - Mood Indigo (Box 92)
  - Moody's Mood (Box 92)
  - Moon River, (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - Moontrane, (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - More Blues (Box 93)
  - Mosaic (Box 93)
  - Motivation (Box 93)
  - Move, (3 folders) (Box 93)
  - Mozzin' (Box 93)
  - Mr. Magic (Box 94)
  - My Blue Heaven (Box 94)
  - My Brotha (Box 94)
  - My Flower, (4 folders) (Box 94)
  - My Heart Stood Still (Box 94)
  - My Man Bill (Box 94)
  - My Romance (Box 94)
  - Naima (Box 94)
  - Naima's Love Song (Box 94)
  - Nardis, (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Nature Boy (Box 94)
  - Nearness, (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Nearness of You, The, (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Nebula (Box 95)
  - Nelba's Struggle, (6 folders) (Box 95)
  - New Blue (Box 95)
  - New Rhumba (Box 95)
  - New York, New York (Box 95)
  - Nickel Whistle (Box 95)
  - Nicole and Nile (Box 95)
  - Night and Day (Box 96)
  - Night in Tunisia, A (arr. Clark) (Box 96)
  - Night in Tunisia, A (arr. Nestico) (Box 96)
  - Nihon Bashi (Box 96)
  - Nioka (Box 96)
  - No Doubt, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - No Moe (Box 96)
  - Not We (Box 96)
  - O Lord We Praise You (Box 96)
  - O.P. (Box 96)
  - O.W. (Box 96)
  - Oahu Lizard, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Occurrence (Box 97)
  - Oclupaca (Box 97)
  - Ode To Vivian, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Of All Things (Box 97)
  - Off Minor (Box 97)
  - Oh Yeah (Box 97)
  - Old Devil Moon (Box 97)
  - Old Folks, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Old King Dooji (Box 97)
  - Oliloqui Valley, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - On a Clear Day (Box 97)
  - On the Edge (Box 97)
  - On the Lion, (3 folders) (Box 97)
  - On the Nile, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - Once Upon a Moon, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One (Box 98)
  - One Bass Hit, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One Finger Snap, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One for Cannon, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One for George, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One for Juan (Box 98)
  - One Man Blues, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - One Note Samba (Box 99)
  - One O'Clock Jump (Box 99)
  - Open Letter to Duke (Box 99)
  - Opus X (Box 99)
  - Organ Grinder, (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Oskar T., (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Out of the Night, (3 folders) (Box 99)
  - Over the Rainbow (Box 99)
  - P.C. Wallbanger (Box 99)
  - P.G., (3 folders) (Box 99)
  - P.J.'s Delight (Box 100)
  - P.S. I Love You (Box 100)
  - Para Tito (Box 100)
  - Parker's Mood (Box 100)
  - Passageway, (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Passion Dance (Box 100)
  - Patio de Juego (Playground) (Box 100)
  - Paul's Pal, (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Peck a Sec, A, (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Peggy's Blue Skylight (Box 101)
  - Pennsylvania 6-5000 (Box 101)
  - Pensativa (Box 101)
  - Perdido, (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Perhaps, (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Philly-N.Y. Junction, (4 folders) (Box 101)
  - Picasso, (2 folders) (Box 102)
  - Picture IV (Box 102)
  - Pieces of 8, 12, and 4, (3 folders) (Box 102)
  - Ping Pong (Box 102)
  - Pink Elephant Magic, (2 folders) (Box 102)
  - Pinocchio (Box 102)
  - Played Twice, (3 folders) (Box 102)
  - Plexus (Box 102)
  - Poron Pon Pon (Box 103)
  - Portrait of Sylvia, (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Positivity, (5 folders) (Box 103)
  - Prelude to a Kiss (Box 104)
  - Prelude, Fugue, and Riffs, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Presence of Dr. B, The, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Prince Albert, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Princess Neh Neh, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Punjab, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Quadrille, Anyone? (Box 104)
  - Queen Bee, The (Box 104)
  - Queer Notions (Box 104)
  - Quiet Fire, (3 folders) (Box 104)
  - Quincy and the Count (Box 105)
  - Quincy's Groove (Box 105)
  - Quit'n Time (Box 105)
  - Radius, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Randi (Box 105)
  - Ray's Idea, (3 folders) (Box 105)
  - Re-Affirmation, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Recordame, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Recorda-Me, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Red Cross, (3 folders) (Box 105)
  - Reed and a Half (Box 106)
  - Reflection, (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Reincarnation of a Lovebird (Box 106)
  - Rejoicin', (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Relativity, (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Remember There's Hope, (3 folders) (Box 106)
  - Remembering Bud (Box 106)
  - Renee (Box 107)
  - Revol (Box 107)
  - Rhapsody for Concert Band and Jazz Ensemble (Box 107)
  - Rhythm Is Our Business (Box 107)
  - Road Time Shuffle (Box 107)
  - Road To Gaza, The (Box 107)
  - Robbins Nest (Box 107)
  - Rock Skippin' (Box 107)
  - Rockabye River (Box 107)
  - Rocker (Box 107)
  - Rockin' in Rhythm, (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Rogi (Box 107)
  - Room 608, (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Rosewood, (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Rosewood, (4 folders) (Box 108)
  - Rotten Kid, The (Box 108)
  - Round Midnight, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Royal Garden Blues (Box 108)
  - Ruby My Dear (Box 108)
  - Runnin Wild (Box 108)
  - Ruth, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - S Go, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - S Wonderful (Box 109)
  - Sacrifice, The, (2 folders) (Box 109)
  - Salsa Ein Burgemeister, (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - Salt Peanuts (Box 109)
  - Samba de Rollins (Box 109)
  - Samba Dubois (Box 109)
  - San Francisco (Box 109)
  - Sans Souci (Box 109)
  - Sao Paolo, (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - Sassy Strut (Box 109)
  - Satellite, (2 folders) (Box 109)
  - Satin Doll (Box 110)
  - Say Yes To Your Best, (4 folders) (Box 110)
  - Scarborough Fair (Box 110)
  - Scenic Route, The, (3 folders) (Box 110)
  - Scratchin in the Gravel (Box 110)
  - Sea Scape (Box 110)
  - Second Balcony Jump (Box 110)
  - Self Twisting Arm, The (Box 110)
  - Senior Blues (Box 110)
  - Senorita Fife, (5 folders) (Box 111)
  - Serpent's Tooth, The, (3 folders) (Box 111)
  - Settin' Red, (3 folders) (Box 111)
  - Seven Steps to Heaven, (2 folders) (Box 111)
  - Sevens, (2 folders) (Box 112)
  - Shade of Jade, A (Box 112)
  - Shawnee (Box 112)
  - Shell Game (Box 112)
  - Shocking News (Box 112)
  - Simone (Box 112)
  - Sing You Sinners (Box 112)
  - Six for Kim, (4 folders) (Box 112)
  - Skippy, (4 folders) (Box 113)
  - Sky Piece, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Slipped Disc (Box 113)
  - Slow Freight, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Smile School (Box 113)
  - Soft as Velvet (Box 113)
  - Soft Shoe, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Soft Shoe (Box 114)
  - Solace (Box 114)
  - Someone to Watch Over Me (Box 114)
  - Something Like a Bird (Box 114)
  - Song Is You, The, (5 folders) (Box 114)
  - Song of Courage, (3 folders) (Box 114)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 115)
  - SOS (Box 115)
  - Soulful Sin (Box 115)
  - Soultrane, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - South Dante, (3 folders) (Box 115)
  - Speak Like a Child, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Special Identity, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Spidit, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Spiral, (4 folders) (Box 116)
  - Splanky (Box 116)
  - Spoons, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - St. Thomas, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - Stablemates, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - Stardust, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - Stella By Starlight, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Step Lightly, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Stepping Stone, (3 folders) (Box 117)
  - Stompin' at the Savoy, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Stormy Monday (Box 117)
  - Straight, No Chaser, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Strait Street (Box 117)
  - Strangers in the Night (Box 117)
  - Strike Up the Band (Box 117)
  - String of Pearls, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Strollin', (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Subliminal Seduction, (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - Such Sweet Thunder (Box 118)
  - Sugar (Box 118)
  - Summer Waltz (Box 118)
  - Sunday Morning (Box 118)
  - Sunny (Box 118)
  - Susan's Waltz (Box 118)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown, (2 folders) (Box 118)
  - Sweet Love of Mine (Box 118)
  - Sweet Talk (Box 118)
  - Swing Low, Sweet Chariot (Box 118)
  - Swing Thing (Box 118)
  - Switch in Time (Box 118)
  - Synergy, (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - Tain't What You Do [Taint Whatcha Do] (Box 119)
  - Take the "A" Train (Box 119)
  - Tall Cotton (Box 119)
  - Tap Dancer, The, (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - Tea Pot, Sweet Georgia Brown (Box 119)
  - Tears I Cannot Hide, The (Box 119)
  - Teeter Totter (Box 119)
  - Tenderly, (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - Tenor Madness (Box 119)
  - Testification, (4 folders) (Box 119)
  - Testimonial, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Thank You (Box 120)
  - Theme, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Theme for Maxine (Box 120)
  - Theme for Penny, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Theme One (Box 120)
  - Theme Two (Box 120)
  - Theme, The (Box 120)
  - Then Came Who? (Box 121)
  - Thermo, (2 folders) (Box 121)
  - Things To Come, (2 folders) (Box 121)
  - Things Will Never (Box 121)
  - Think of One, (5 folders) (Box 121)
  - Third Day, The (Box 122)
  - This Is for Albert (Box 122)
  - Those Were the Days (Box 122)
  - Three and Me (Box 122)
  - Thumbs Up (Box 122)
  - Tickle Toe (Box 122)
  - Tico Tico (Box 122)
  - Time Off (Box 122)
  - Time To Go, (3 folders) (Box 122)
  - Time's Mirror (Box 122)
  - Timothy, (2 folders) (Box 122)
  - Tip Toe (Box 122)
  - Tokyo Blues, The (Box 122)
  - Tones for Joan's Bones, (3 folders) (Box 123)
  - Too Deep for the Ocean (Box 123)
  - Tragic Magic, (2 folders) (Box 123)
  - Train Shuffle, (2 folders) (Box 123)
  - Trane Connections (Box 123)
  - Trials of Trust and Treachery, The (Box 123)
  - Tribute To Art Fern, A (Box 123)
  - Tribute to the Duke (Box 123)
  - Troica, (2 folders) (Box 123)
  - True Friends, (5 folders) (Box 124)
  - Tullio Meets the Two Marizios, (4 folders) (Box 124)
  - Turnpike (Box 124)
  - Turnpike, (3 folders) (Box 125)
  - Twelve Inch (Box 125)
  - Twilight Town (Box 125)
  - Two Bass Hit (Box 125)
  - Ugly Beauty, (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Un Poco Loco, (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Una Mas, (3 folders) (Box 125)
  - Unbroken Line, (3 folders) (Box 126)
  - Undecided (Box 126)
  - Up Close and Personal, (4 folders) (Box 126)
  - Up Jumped Spring (Box 126)
  - Us (Box 126)
  - Us Is Too, (2 folders) (Box 126)
  - Use it Blues (Box 126)
  - Valery's Changes (Box 126)
  - Valse Robin (Box 126)
  - Ven Devorame Otra Vez (Box 126)
  - Vicious Cycle, The, (3 folders) (Box 126)
  - Vines, (3 folders) (Box 127)
  - Vision, The (Box 127)
  - Voices of Jazz, (5 folders) (Box 127)
  - Voices of Jazz, (2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Voodoo Lady, (2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Wail (Box 128)
  - Wake Up Call (Box 128)
  - Walkin and Swingin (Box 128)
  - Waltz Boogie (Box 128)
  - Waltz for Aunt Marie (Box 128)
  - Waltz for Debby, (3 folders) (Box 129)
  - Waltz for Ima (Box 129)
  - Waltz for Zweetie, (3 folders) (Box 129)
  - Waltz Little (Box 129)
  - Waltz Medley (Box 129)
  - Waltz You Swang for Me, The (Box 129)
  - Warm Valley, (2 folders) (Box 129)
  - Wave (Box 130)
  - We Be Jammin' (Box 130)
  - We See, (4 folders) (Box 130)
  - Wednesday Night Prayer Meeting (Box 130)
  - Well Alright Then, (2 folders) (Box 130)
  - We'll Be Together Again, (3 folders) (Box 131)
  - Western Reunion, (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - What Am I Here For (Box 131)
  - What Ya Want (Box 131)
  - What's New Medley (Box 131)
  - When I Fall In Love (Box 131)
  - Whenever the Blues (Box 131)
  - Where's the Time (Box 131)
  - Whirling, (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - Whirlwind (Box 131)
  - Wiggle Waggle (Box 131)
  - Willie B. (Box 131)
  - Windstar, (3 folders) (Box 132)
  - Witchcraft (Box 132)
  - With Love, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Woodchopper's Ball (Box 132)
  - Woody 1 - On The New Ark (Box 132)
  - Woody I and the New Ark (Box 132)
  - Work (Box 132)
  - Work Song, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - World (Box 132)
  - Worlds Apart, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Worlds of Drums, (2 folders) (Box 133)
  - Worry Later (Box 133)
  - Ya Gotta Try (Box 133)
  - Yardbird Suite (Box 133)
  - Yeah, (2 folders) (Box 133)
  - Yeah Man (Box 133)
  - Y-Not (Box 133)
  - You and the Night and the Music, (4 folders) (Box 133)
  - You Can Count On Me (Box 134)
  - You Got It (Box 134)
  - You or Me (Box 134)
  - Miscellaneous (52nd - Circean) (Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous (Ciribiribin - Groovin') (Box 136)
  - Miscellaneous (Half - Made) (Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous (Maids - Rivbia) (Box 138)
  - Miscellaneous (Roden - Swinging) (Box 139)
  - Miscellaneous (TBA - You're) (Box 140)
- Series V: Oversize Music Manuscripts, (66 boxes)
  Approximately 540 compositions for jazz ensemble, including both published and unpublished materials. This series contains a substantial collection of Jeffrey's compositions and arrangements for the Duke University Jazz Ensemble, including works written for both standard big band instrumentation as well as non-standard instrumentations. It additionally contains commercially published compositions and other miscellaneous manuscripts.
  The series consists chiefly of full scores organized by composition title, with different versions and copies of the same composition grouped together. Most of the materials are undated. Includes hand-written manuscripts, photocopies, and manuscripts produced on a laser printer. Many are unbound; please handle carefully and keep pages in their original order.
  Series also includes seven boxes of unidentified scores and manuscript fragments, placed at the end of the series.
  - 1st Night Blues, (2 copies) (Box 141)
  - 502 Blues, (2 copies) (Box 141)
  - 91-1 (Box 141)
  - A La Mode (Box 141)
  - Acirema (Box 141)
  - Adam's Apple (Box 141)
  - Advance Notice (Box 141)
  - African Aztec (Box 141)
  - After The Morning, (2 copies) (Box 141)
  - Again Again, (2 copies) (Box 141)
  - Air Mail Special (Box 141)
  - Air-Mail (Box 141)
  - Alice In Wonderland (Box 141)
  - Alone Together (Box 141)
  - Alterations, (2 copies) (Box 142)
  - Amanda's Song, (3 copies) (Box 142)
  - Angelica, (2 copies) (Box 142)
  - Animal Instincts, (3 copies) (Box 142)
  - Anone (Box 143)
  - Apple Turnover, (4 copies) (Box 143)
  - Apres Vous (Box 143)
  - Arabia (Box 143)
  - Armageddon (Box 143)
  - Art Of War, The (Box 143)
  - As Time Goes By (Box 143)
  - Assessment, (2 copies) (Box 143)
  - Athlolete (Box 143)
  - Attainment (Box 143)
  - Autumn In New York, (3 copies) (Box 143)
  - B Flat Blues (Box 144)
  - Back In The Days (Box 144)
  - Backstairs (Box 144)
  - Balue Bolivar Balues Are (Box 144)
  - Basie (Box 144)
  - Be Bop Irishman (Box 144)
  - Be Careful Of Dreams (Box 144)
  - Bean And The Boys, (3 copies) (Box 144)
  - Beatrice (Box 144)
  - Beethoven Meets The Millenium In Spain (Box 145)
  - Believers, The (Box 145)
  - Bella Carolina (Box 145)
  - Benji's Bounce (Box 145)
  - Bernie's Tune (Box 145)
  - Bess You Is My Woman (Box 145)
  - Bessie's Blues (Box 145)
  - Beyond The Blue (Box 145)
  - Big Bad Jam (Box 145)
  - Big Beat, The, (2 copies) (Box 145)
  - Big P (Box 145)
  - Bird, The (Box 145)
  - Black Nile (Box 146)
  - Blue Daniel (Box 146)
  - Blue Devil, The (Box 146)
  - Blue Monk (Box 146)
  - Blue Skies (Box 146)
  - Blue Skies (1944) (Box 146)
  - Blues A La Burgess, (3 copies) (Box 146)
  - Blues Behavior, (2 copies) (Box 146)
  - Blues For Brown, (2 copies) (Box 146)
  - Blues For Corinne (Box 146)
  - Blues In The Pocket, (2 copies) (Box 146)
  - Blues On The Corner (Box 147)
  - Body And Soul, (2 copies) (Box 147)
  - Bold Steps, (3 copies) (Box 147)
  - Bolivia (Box 147)
  - Bondage (Box 147)
  - Boogie Stop Shuffle, (2 copies) (Box 147)
  - Boston Bernie (Box 147)
  - Bouncing With Bud (Box 147)
  - Bourr'ee (Box 147)
  - Brand New World, (2 copies) (Box 148)
  - Brand X, (3 copies) (Box 148)
  - Brasilia (Box 148)
  - Bright Mississippi, (2 copies) (Box 148)
  - Broadway (Box 148)
  - Brookland (Box 148)
  - Brooklyn Nights (Box 148)
  - Brother Ray (Box 148)
  - Brownie Speaks, (2 copies) (Box 149)
  - Bud's Blues, (3 copies) (Box 149)
  - Bu's Delight, (3 copies) (Box 149)
  - Bu's Delight, (2 copies) (Box 150)
  - Buzzard Song, The (Box 150)
  - Bye Ya, (2 copies) (Box 150)
  - C Jam Blues (Box 151)
  - C T A (Box 151)
  - Cabu (Box 151)
  - Candu (Box 151)
  - Can't Help Loving Dat Man (Box 151)
  - Captain Blued (Box 151)
  - Caravan, (4 copies) (Box 151)
  - Caravanserai (Box 151)
  - Carolina Backroads (Box 151)
  - Celia (Box 151)
  - Century Rag, (2 copies) (Box 152)
  - Ceora (Box 152)
  - Chanice, (2 copies) (Box 152)
  - Chedlike (Box 152)
  - Cherokee (Box 152)
  - Cherry Juice, (2 copies) (Box 152)
  - Chess Players, The (Box 152)
  - Chevy Chase Fox Trot, (2 copies) (Box 152)
  - Chi-Chi (Box 152)
  - Chips (Box 152)
  - Christopher Columbus (Box 152)
  - Clarion (Box 152)
  - Close Enough For Love (Box 152)
  - Coffee Pot, (4 copies) (Box 153)
  - Confab In Tempo (Box 153)
  - Confirmation (Box 154)
  - Congeniality (Box 154)
  - Cosmic Echoes (Box 154)
  - Cottontail (Box 154)
  - Countdown (Box 154)
  - Cram 'n Exam, (2 copies) (Box 154)
  - Cruisin', (2 copies) (Box 154)
  - Cry For Understanding, A (Box 154)
  - Cry Of Hunger, (2 copies) (Box 154)
  - Cubano Chant (Box 154)
  - Cubanza (Box 154)
  - Cubicle (Box 154)
  - Cycles (Box 154)
  - Daily Affirmation, (3 copies) (Box 155)
  - Dance Of The Infidels, (4 copies) (Box 155)
  - Dark And Lovely, (2 copies) (Box 155)
  - Dark Powers (Box 155)
  - Dear John, (3 copies) (Box 155)
  - Delores (Box 155)
  - Derricksterity, (3 copies) (Box 156)
  - Deux Battements De Coeur (Box 156)
  - Dickie's Dream (Box 156)
  - Dig (Box 156)
  - Do Nothin (Box 156)
  - Dolphin Dance (Box 156)
  - Donna Lee, (3 copies) (Box 156)
  - Donna Lee, (2 copies) (Box 157)
  - Don't Let It Go (Box 157)
  - Don't Take Your Love (Box 157)
  - Down Basie Street (Box 157)
  - Dream Little Boy Dream (Box 157)
  - Druid (Box 157)
  - Drum Suite (Box 157)
  - Duke Ellington Medley (Box 157)
  - Ebony Moonbeams, (2 copies) (Box 158)
  - Egg Hunt, (2 copies) (Box 158)
  - Egyptian Dune Dance (Box 158)
  - Einstein (Box 158)
  - Elija, (2 copies) (Box 158)
  - Elsa (Box 158)
  - Emily, (2 copies) (Box 158)
  - Epistrophy, (3 copies) (Box 158)
  - Eronel, (3 copies) (Box 159)
  - Estevanico's Journey (Box 159)
  - Eternal Triangle (Box 159)
  - Evidence, (4 copies) (Box 159)
  - Exhilaration, (2 copies) (Box 159)
  - Extrasensory Perception (Box 159)
  - Fact Of Loss, The (Box 160)
  - Feed The People (Box 160)
  - Firefly (Box 160)
  - Float Like A Butterfly, Sting Like A Bee, (3 copies) (Box 160)
  - Foggy Day, A (Box 160)
  - Folklore (Box 160)
  - Folks Meet Our Drummer (Box 160)
  - Footprints, (2 copies) (Box 160)
  - For The Elders, (2 copies) (Box 160)
  - Forever Sonny (Box 160)
  - Four Nigerian Dances (Box 160)
  - Four On The Outside (Box 161)
  - Freedom Shout (Box 161)
  - Friday The Thirteenth (Box 161)
  - Fried Bananas (Box 161)
  - Friend Or Foe (Box 161)
  - Fruit, The (Box 161)
  - Fulton Street Theme (Box 161)
  - Fum (Box 161)
  - Funny Blues (Box 161)
  - Gabrielle's Balloon (Box 162)
  - Gentle Rain (Box 162)
  - Ghost Butter, (2 copies) (Box 162)
  - Giant Steps (Box 162)
  - Giddybug Gallop (Box 162)
  - Ginger Flower Song, (2 copies) (Box 162)
  - Gingerbread Boy (Box 162)
  - Glass Enclosure (Box 162)
  - Gone, (3 copies) (Box 162)
  - Good Bait (Box 163)
  - Good Life, The, (2 copies) (Box 163)
  - Gorilla Shuffle (Box 163)
  - Gotsta' Be A Better Way, (2 copies) (Box 163)
  - Grand Mal (Box 163)
  - Grant, (2 copies) (Box 163)
  - Growing Pains, (3 copies) (Box 163)
  - Hallucinations, (2 copies) (Box 164)